Recall that this peritoneum is established concurrently with this developmental phase
我提醒您，这个腹膜的形成与外体腔整合为内体腔的这个发育阶段同时发生。
of the integration of the external coelom into an internal coelom.
即外体腔整合为内体腔。
This is the primitive establishment of my peritoneum.
这就是我的腹膜的原始形成。
First, there is polarity; there is information regarding my neural tube,
我首先有极性，我有关于我的神经管的信息，
there is the growth of this neural tube, which is organized in space and time
我有这个神经管的生长，它在空间和时间中被组织，
by the fluidic reorganization of my embryo, i.e., the early development
通过我的胚胎的流体重新组织，也就是说，我的胚胎的早期发育。
of my embryo.
我的胚胎的。
my primitive aortas, it's a whole endeavor
我的原始主动脉，这整个过程都在寻找，
to return towards its midline.
为了使其回归到其中线。
It does everything to return to its center.
我尽一切努力回归自我。
And the axis to which it will return is this aorta.
而我将回归的轴线，就是这条主动脉。
The peritoneum corresponds to this development.
腹膜，它响应这个发育。
It is the outcome, it is the expression of this development.
它是最终结果，它是这个发育的表达。
There is the amniotic cavity, vitelline cavity,
我有羊膜腔，卵黄囊腔，
the embryonic pedicle, and all around here,
胚柄，以及这里周围的一切，
all around, which envelops.
周围，包裹着。
This is referred to as the external coelom.
这就是我们所说的外体腔。
In the subsequent developmental phase, we will see how this external coelom is
在接下来的发育阶段，我们将看到这个外体腔是如何
integrated into an internal coelom.
整合为内体腔的。
This occurs synchronously between the establishment of my
这同步发生，在我的
primitive digestive tube
原始消化管的形成
and the establishment of the surrounding envelopment, my peritoneum
以及周围包裹物的形成，我的
visceral and my parietal peritoneum.
脏层腹膜和我的壁层腹膜之间。
And between my visceral peritoneum,
而在我的脏层腹膜之间，
and my parietal peritoneum, a fluid integrates, which comes from the
和我的壁层腹膜之间，有一种液体整合进来，它来自
external coelom to
外体腔，为了
become the internal coelom, which will later be called the intra-peritoneal fluid.
成为内体腔，之后将被称为腹腔内液体。
There exists no
不存在任何
intra-peritoneal organ; there exist only peritonealized organs. With few
腹腔内器官，只存在腹膜化的器官。几乎
exceptions, in
没有例外，在
the woman where there is an opening between the peritoneum and the external world
女性的腹膜与外界之间存在一个开口
with respect to the organization
相对于其组织而言的外部
of the fallopian tubes. This is why we can have an...
输卵管。这就是为什么我们可能会有...
extra-uterine process. The uterus is merely a concentration of posterior parietal peritoneum
宫外孕。子宫，它只是壁层腹膜的集中
which condenses, and the lines that will form here will constitute the fallopian tubes
后方凝结，在这里形成的线条将形成输卵管
towards the opening of my peritoneal cavity. The amniotic cavity, the vitelline cavity
朝向我的腹腔开口。羊膜腔，卵黄囊腔
and the embryonic pellicle. There is this very significant growth
和胚胎膜。存在这种生长
of the whole,
整体的非常重要的生长，
it grows, organizes, and delineates itself.
它生长、组织并划定界限。
Next, to assist us, we will make a section, we will turn this section towards us, and
接着，为了帮助我们，我们将进行一个切面，并把这个切面转向我们，
thus it is the same drawing, but in another dimension, where this time, I
所以这是相同的图画，但在另一个维度，这次我
see my amniotic cavity, my vitelline cavity, I see the
看到我的羊膜腔、我的卵黄囊腔，我看到
notochordal process which is one of the subtle drivers for
脊索过程，它是其中一个微妙的驱动力，用于
development, I see the formation of my neural tube, which is the driver
发育。我看到我的神经管的形成，它是驱动力
for growth.
用于生长。
It is it that guides by its expansion, but which is guided in its growth
是它通过其爆发来引导，但其生长方向受到引导
by the notochord.
通过脊索。
There is this amniotic cavity which is completely shaped by the neural tube and by my aortas
存在这个羊膜腔，它完全通过神经管和我的主动脉
which will develop on either side here at the origin of my neural tube,
它们将在这里我的神经管起点两侧发育，
oriented and organized in the developmental space of this embryo.
在这个胚胎的发育空间中被引导和组织。
The very significant growth in
非常重要的生长，呈
trough-like shape of my embryo,
我的胚胎的沟槽状，
the aortas appearing, the closure of my neural tube, gradually
出现的主动脉，我的神经管的闭合，渐渐地
we do not see it,
我们看不到它，
but there will be the approximation of my aortas, because they will not grow at the same
但我的主动脉将靠近，因为它们不会以相同的速度生长，
rate, we see them, and at the moment I have this phase of approximation, you
速度，我们看到它们，当我处于这个靠近阶段时，你
see, they were there,
看，它们在那里，
these two tubes began to move towards the center, bring the information, but do not grow
它们开始向中心移动，这两个管子带来信息，但不生长
at all at the same rate, and all the rest around grows, well, the only possible resultant
根本不是以相同的速度，而周围的一切都在生长，那么唯一的结果
possible
可能的
it originates from water.
它来自水。
move towards the center, which reorganizes the longitudinal axis of the embryo, this
趋向中心，这重新组织了胚胎的纵向发育过程，
which reorganizes the
重新组织了
overall organization, which means that, okay, I move towards where I am attracted.
整体的定位，这使得我被吸引到哪里，我就去哪里。
it's like
这就像
an attraction that occurs, which guides this movement. Here, there is now
一种吸引力正在发生，引导着这个运动，现在这里有了
a space that forms with the
一个空间正在形成，伴随着
somatopleure, the splanchnopleure, and at the same time, we see the neural tube, the approximation of my
体壁中胚层和脏壁中胚层，同时我们看到神经管，我的主动脉的靠近，
aortas, and we see the formation
主动脉，我们看到形成
at the same time, at the same moment, of my developing digestive tube.
同时，在同一时刻，我的消化管正在发育。
And we see on this section that the fluid which is here
我们在这张切片上看到，这里的液体
gradually begins to be enclosed here,
逐渐开始被封闭在这里，
to integrate into a space here.
进入并整合到这里的一个空间中。
And in this space, if we continue the development,
在这个空间里，如果我们继续观察发育，
what is very important, and it is not expressed in this drawing,
非常重要的是，这张图上没有表达出来的是，
is to see this within a growth process.
是要在一个生长过程中看待它。
Look at the formation of my tube,
看看我的管的形成，
and look at this movement here.
看看这里的这个运动。
of my amniotic cavity which comes completely, this time, enveloped
我的羊膜腔，这次完全被包裹
on the sides,
在两侧，
but also anteriorly, posteriorly, like a balloon that is
但也向前，向后，就像一个气球，它被
fixed here and which
固定在这里，并且
comes to surround itself anteriorly. And it is in this movement here, by my aortas which restrain,
在前面环绕。正是在这里的这个运动中，通过我的主动脉的制动作用，
by my notochord which organizes the process, I have the integration of
通过我的脊索组织着这个过程，我有了
my external coelom.
我的胚外体腔。
Into an internal coelom; this is a section that will be located near my umbilical cord.
成为一个胚内体腔，这是一张位于我的脐带附近的切片。
I can make the same section further away, here or here.
我可以在更远的地方做同样的切片，在这里或这里。
This image changes slightly.
这张图像会稍微改变。
Either I have this connection with the future umbilical cord, the remnant of
要么我有了这种与未来脐带的连接，即
the vitelline vesicle,
卵黄囊的残余，
which will integrate with the embryonic pedicle,
将与胚柄整合，
or another time, another movement, where I will just see the integration
或者在另一个时间、另一个运动中，我将只看到整合
of my peritoneal cavity.
我的腹膜腔。
Do not forget, I am attached by my umbilical cord.
别忘了，我通过脐带连接。
We will make the same section, but this time more anteriorly.
我们将进行相同的切面，但这次更靠前。
And at that level, I will truly see the integration.
在这个层面上，我将真正看到整合。
Always the same movement.
始终是相同的运动。
Therefore, my amniotic cavity is very important,
所以我的羊膜腔非常重要，
because not only was it a small pouch that appeared,
因为它不仅是一个出现的小囊，
afterwards, it will completely invade the space.
之后它将完全侵占空间。
And here, we arrive at
此时，我们进入
the image, where it completely closes there, at this stage, and
这个图像，在这个阶段它完全闭合，并且
I am here. I have the integration
我在这里。我看到了整合
of my external coelom into an internal coelom. I have the integration
我的外体腔整合为内体腔。我看到了整合
of the external coelom into an
外部体腔整合为
internal coelom. This is an important image because we will see that your
内部体腔。这是一个重要的图像，因为我们将看到您的
digestive tract,
消化道，
not only is it filled with bacteria.
不仅充满了细菌。
A genome contains information from your environment.
一个基因组，它包含您环境的信息。
So it contains even genetic information.
所以它甚至包含遗传信息。
It is filled with genes that participate in your own development.
它充满了参与您自身发展的基因。
A holobiont that encompasses this entire genetic environment,
一个全息生物，它包含了所有这些遗传环境，
that you begin to prepare, to integrate,
您开始准备、整合，
which will be completely dynamized at the moment of birth.
它将在出生时完全被激活。
Where there, you will completely prepare the humus.
届时，您将完全准备好腐殖质。
the flora that will completely explode in its dynamic,
菌群将在其动态中完全爆发，
but upon which you rely for your development.
但您依赖它来发展。
And we know that these genes that participate in your flora
我们知道，这些参与您菌群的基因
exchange with your brain, exchange with your thought.
与您的大脑交换，与您的思想交换。
You think through the type of bacteria you have.
您的思考方式取决于您拥有的细菌类型。
Hence the importance of finding an adequate environment.
因此，找到一个适宜的环境至关重要。
in which you feel good.
在其中你感觉良好。
The environment in which I evolve also makes me evolve,
我所处的环境也促使我发展，
because all of this contributes to your genetics and your epigenetics,
因为这一切都参与你的遗传学和表观遗传学，
that is, to your permanent adaptive capacity.
也就是说，你的永久适应能力。
First image of your peritoneal cavity,
这是你的腹膜腔的第一张图像，
of this peritoneum taking shape.
正在显现的腹膜。
It has both a metabolic function,
它同时具有代谢功能，
it has a protective function,
它具有保护功能，
it has a mechanical function.
它具有机械功能。
it participates in your motility, it participates in your mobility
它参与你的运动能力，它参与你的活动度，
and it is integrated by your motility.
并且它被你的自发运动所整合。
Its origin is from the mesoderm, which means it has a mechanical function,
它的起源是中胚层，这意味着它具有机械功能，
a supportive function and a mobility function. One of the roles, there
支持功能和活动功能。其中一个作用是，
is a kind
在中胚层层面有一种细胞特化，我们称之为间皮细胞，
of cellular specialization at the level of the mesoderm, which we call mesothelial cells,
它们将使...能够...
which will provide the possibility...
使腹膜能够捕获腹膜内和腹膜间的信息。
for the peritoneum to capture inter- and intra-peritoneal information.
这是一层非常宽广的浆膜。
It is a very large serous membrane.
我认为它大约有2平方米。
I think it is approximately 2 square meters.
C'est une membrane serreuse qui est très large.
Je pense qu'elle fait aux environs de 2 mètres carrés.
Je pense qu'elle fait aux environs de 2 mètres carrés.